That's the feeling we want to address
with this treatment.
Yeah. Or you could pitch in, grab a nostril
and help me get this face off.
(Amy:)Come on. You can do this.
(Sheldon:)You don't know what it's like
to feel completely frustrated.
(Sheldon:)To have a desire build up within you
and be denied any opportunity for release.
(Amy:)Yeah, sounds like a drag.
(Penny:)Okay, help me out here.
Why does he love this show so much?
(Bernadette:)Well, there was action, it was funny.
(Bernadette:)I mean, you do get that usually
the monster chases the pretty girl...
(Bernadette:)...but this time the pretty girl
chases the monsters?
(Penny:)Yippee, it's backwards, I get it.